John and Ginny Dildine collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
John and Ginny Dildine collection 1956-1970
1957-1964
AFC 1975/001
Dildine, John
Dildine, Ginny
175 items
119 sound tape reels: analog; 7 in.
24 sound tape reels: analog; 10 in.
12 sound tape reels: analog; 5 in.
manuscripts: 1 folder.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of sound recordings of Washington, D.C. area folk music radio programs on WASH and WAMU-FM, hosted by John Dildine, with live interviews, and featuring some previously recorded selections. The collection also includes sound recordings of concerts, folk festivals (including selections from the Fox Hollow Folk Festival, 1968 and 1969) and other folk music events in Maryland; Virginia; St. Louis, Missouri; New York state, and other locations. Collection includes performances and interviews with well known musicians from the United States, Great Britain, Scotland, and Ireland; plus a few shows featuring recordings of music from Kenya and from India. Some items are dubs of commercial recordings.
Provenance
John and Ginny Dildine; Donation; 1975.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Related Material
John Dildine and Ginny Dildine papers, 1957-2014, bulk 1957-1995.
John Dildine collection
Access and Restrictions
The John and Ginny Dildine collection is open to research. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Certain restrictions to use or copying of materials may apply.
Biographical Note
John Dildine and Ginny Dildine became familiar figures on the folk music scene in the 1960s, performing at various festivals, schools, and other venues. Around 1965 they began to incorporate puppetry into their stage performances. The puppets were designed by Ginny and either hand-operated or worn as costumes. Over the years the Dildine children (Scott, Debbie, and Connie) joined their parents onstage for musical performances, and to help operate the puppets. Among John's many accomplishments, he was also the host of folk music programs on Washington, D.C.-area radio stations WASH and WAMU-FM (from 1957-1970) and was the first president of the Folklore Society of Greater Washington (1964-1965).
Scope and Content
Collection of sound recordings of Washington, D.C. area folk music radio programs on WASH and WAMU-FM, hosted by John Dildine, with live interviews, and featuring some previously recorded selections. The collection also includes sound recordings of concerts, folk festivals (including selections from the Fox Hollow Folk Festival, 1968 and 1969) and other folk music events in Maryland; Virginia; St. Louis, Missouri; New York state, and other locations. Collection includes performances and interviews with well known musicians from the United States, Great Britain, Scotland, and Ireland; plus a few shows featuring recordings of music from Kenya and from India. Some items are dubs of commercial recordings.
Arrangement
The John Dildine and Ginny Dildine collection is organized by sound recording. The sound recordings have been digitized, with separate digital files for each side of a tape. Summaries for each tape (or tape side) are from Marshall Howard Kramer's listening notes. Where listening notes are not available, summaries are inferred from earlier inventories.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Aaron, Tossi; Abrahams, Roger D.; Beers, Bob, 1920-1972; Beers, Evelyne; Carawan, Guy; Clayton, Paul, 1931-1967; Cohen, John, 1932-2019; Collins, Judy, 1939-; Damron, Allen Wayne; Daniels, Charlotte; Dildine, Ginny; Dildine, John; Ennis, Seamus; Fariña, Richard; Foss, George; Hedin, Carol; Hester, Carolyn; Hurt, Mississippi John, 1892-1966; Kennedy, Norman, 1934-; Kweskin, Jim,--Interviews.; Martin-Perdue, Nancy J.; McGhee, Brownie, 1915-1996; McGhee, Brownie, 1915-1996,--Interviews.; Paley, Tom; Paley, Tom,--Interviews.; Paton, Sandy; Perdue, Charles L., 1930-2010; Sear, Dave; Seeger, Mike, 1933-2009; Seeger, Peggy, 1935-; Seeger, Pete, 1919-2014--Interviews.; Terry, Sonny; Terry, Sonny--Interviews.; Von Schmidt, Eric; Wilkins, Robert, 1896-1987
Organizations
Annual Fox Hollow Festival of Traditional Music and Arts.; Fox Hollow Folk Festival.; New Lost City Ramblers; WAMU-FM (Radio station: Washington, D.C.); WASH-FM (Radio station: Washington, D.C.)
Subjects
Ballads, English.; Bluegrass music.; Blues (Music); Folk festivals--United States.; Folk music--England.; Folk music--India.; Folk music--Ireland.; Folk music--Kenya.; Folk music--Scotland.; Folk music--United States.; Folk music--Washington (D.C.); Folk songs, English.; Old-time music.; Popular music--United States--1951-1960.; Popular music--United States--1961-1970.; Popular music--United States--1971-1980.; Working class--Songs and music.
Places
Washington (D.C.)
Form/Genre
Folk music radio programs.; Radio airchecks.; Radio interviews.
Container List
- Manuscripts
  - Notes about the recordings., 1 folder (Container 1)
- Sound Recordings
  Sound recordings are listed below by SR number, with listening notes and logs per tape side. For a listing by performer see "Contents by Performer Name" (please note: This listing was created from an earlier inventory, and there may be some numbering inaccuracies.)
  - AFC 1975/001: SR001, Recorded: ca. 1956-1957, RXG 0812; 14:15
    John Runge is a professional singer and guitarist who frequently appears on British radio, television and recitals. He was on the faculty of Phillips-Exeter Academy, Exeter, New Hampshire during 1956-1957 as an exchange teacher. Runge sings and plays guitar on all songs.
    Start Runge talks about England being called the land without music.
    1:05 Man is for the Woman Made A song by Henry Purcell.
    2:12 Greensleeves
    4:05 Soldier, Soldier Will You Marry Me Cecil Sharp collected this version.
    6:08 The Foggy Dew
    6:50 The Foggy Dew a different version
    8:09 Lord Randall
    9:57 The Water is Wide
    12:00 Old Daddy Fox
    12:49 The Barley Mow
  - AFC 1975/001: SR002 (1), Recorded: 1957-11-13, RXG 0693; 30:07
    Uneven recording quality; seems to be a single microphone and a tape recorder; sometimes the instruments overwhelm the vocals.
    Start "I'm a Child a Fightin'" Mike Seeger, Tom Paley, others
    05:27 "Jackie Frasier" Tom Paley
    10:25 "The Cuckoo" John Cohen
    12:30 "Here Rattler Here" group led by John Cohen
    14:55 "Skip to My Lou" Sam Anderson (lap dulcimer)
    15:30 [unintelligible spoken word]
    15:45 "Molly and Tenbrooks" Tom Paley and Mike Seeger
    18:45 "Shady Grove" John Cohen
    21:00 "Old Mother Hare" Tom Paley and Mike Seeger
    23:25 [instrumental, title unknown] Tom Paley and Mike Seeger
    24:16 "Cripple Creek" Mike Seeger and Tom Paley
    26:30 "Ida Red" Mike Seeger and Tom Paley
    28:10 "Old Joe Clark" Tom Paley and Mike Seeger
  - AFC 1975/001: SR002 (2), Recorded: 1957-11-22, RXG 0693; 30:51
    Uneven recording quality; seems to be a single microphone and a tape recorder; sometimes the instruments overwhelm the vocals. Handwritten notes in the collection folder states: "Selections #1 – 8 from Hoot 3 at Cabin john Recreation Center in Cabin John, Maryland in 11-22-57. Selections #9 – 20 from Hoot 4 at Rock Creek Recreation Center in Chevy Chase, Md. On 12-13-57".
    Start "Sail Away Ladies" group led by Tom Paley
    2:25 "Midnight Special" group led by Tom Paley
    7:07 "Little Maggie" group led by Tom Paley
    9:58 "Old Woman with the Seven Little Devils" group led by Tom Paley
    13:20 "There'll Come a Time" Hutch Morris and Tom Paley
    18:05 "The Fossil Society" ("Truthful James") Sam Anderson
    21:45 "The Monkey and the Fish" John Kauffman
    23:50 "Railroad Bill" Tom Paley
    26:55 "Sail Upon the Deep Blue Sea" Mike Seeger
    29:50 "Tra La La" group
  - AFC 1975/001: SR003, Recorded: Winter 1957-1958, RXG 0694; 15:05
    Recording quality is very good. Handwritten notes in the collection folder states: "Christy's Studio winter 1957-58."
    Start "Henry Lee" Chris and Pixie Christy
    3:00 "Ain't Got No Place to Lay My Head" Chris and Pixie
    4:55 "When are you comin' to see me" [first line] Chris and Pixie [The song's title may be "My Sye." It is a courting song. The melody seems to be the same as "Buffalo Boys"]
    6:35 "Sierra Peaks" or "Tying a Knot in the Devil's Tail" Pixie
    8:25 "Young Rogers the Miller" Chris and Pixie [The tune is the same as "Sweet Betsy from Pike"]
    10:06 "Once there was a Quaker lover" [first line] Chris and Pixie [The title may be "Quaker Lover"]
    11:42 "First he made the sun" [first line] Chris and Pixie [ the title may be "The Creation"]
    12:55 "Stagolee" or "Slackolee" Chris [Laws I 15]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR004, side A, Recorded: 1957, RXG 0695; 32:22
    This is a live, studio recording for a radio broadcast by John Dildine with guest performers Paul Clayton and Roger Abrahams. The program is called "Folk Music." It was broadcast on WASH FM.
    Start Theme song: "Railroad Bill" by Etta Baker [recording]
    2:51 Talking John Dildine, Paul Clayton, Roger Abrahams
    10:25 "Delia" or "Delia's Gone" Clayton
    12:53 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    14:54 "The Cruel War is Raging" Roger Abrahams
    17:39 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    18:30 "One Morning in May" Clayton
    20:30 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    31:40 Introduction to a recording of "Marching Jaybird" by [Lacy Phillips] Clayton
    32:15 End of side A
  - AFC 1975/001: SR004, side B, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0695; 29:40
    Continuation of John Dildine's radio broadcast.
    Start End of "Marching Jaybird" [only a few seconds were recorded]
    0:15 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    1:06 "Greenwood Sidey" Abrahams
    3:45 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    4:14 "Black Dog Blues" Clayton
    5:40 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    6:05 "Make Me a Pallet on Your Floor" Abrahams
    8:09 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    8:40 "Duncan and Brady" Clayton
    11:36 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    13:10 "Bury Me Beneath the Willow" Abrahams (guitar and vocal), Paul Clayton (vocal)
    14:20 Talking John Dildine, Paul Clayton, Roger Abrahams
    16:50 "2 Dollar Bill" Abrahams (guitar and vocal), Clayton (vocal)
    18:15 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    20:30 "Payday and Coal Creek" Clayton
    22:43 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    23:12 "If He's Gone, Let Him Go" Abrahams
    25:17 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    26:00 "Rolling Home" Clayton (guitar and vocal); others (harmony on the chorus)
    28:24 Talking Dildine, Clayton, Abrahams
    28:43 Reprise - "Rolling Home" Paul Clayton (guitar and vocal); others (harmony on the chorus); Dildine - talking
    29:40 End of side B
  - AFC 1975/001: SR005, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0696; 28:30
    Good recording quality
    Start An unidentified male introduces the performers: Roger Abrahams, Paul Clayton and Gina Glaser
    0:58 It Takes a Worried man to Sing a Worried Song" Glaser, Clayton and Abrahams
    3:12 Clayton introduces the next song
    4:02 "Springfield Mountain" Clayton
    6:00 "The Cuckoo" Glaser
    9:12 "Slippin' Around" Abrahams Also known as "Make Me a Pallet on Your Floor"
    12:08 (tuning guitars)
    12:50 "If He's Gone, Let him Go" Abrahams and Glaser
    15:48 "Blood Red Roses" Clayton and Abrahams (a cappella)
    18:12 "Polly Vaughn" Clayton
    21:35 "Greenland Whalers" Clayton
    23:50 "Red Rosy Bush" Glaser
    26:08 "Siúli A Rún" (Gaelic) Glaser First line: "I wish I was up yonder hill, 'tis there I'd sit and cry my fill"
    28:30 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR006, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0697; 27:21
    This is probably a continuation of SR005. Good recording quality
    Start Introduction to the next song Paul Clayton
    1:00 "Jesse James" Clayton
    4:07 Introduction to the next song and discussion of the Appalachian dulcimer (also known as the lap dulcimer) Clayton
    5:15 "The Ballad of Masse Grove" Clayton Also known as "The Ballad of Matty Groves"
    9:47 "The Devil and the Famer" Clayton
    13:30 Folk tale, "Coon Skin Hunting" told by Clayton
    15:45 "Old Blue" Clayton
    17:25 "Done Laid Around" Clayton, Roger Abrahams and Gina Glaser First line: "Done laid around and stayed around this old town too long". Also known as "Gotta Travel On".
    20:08 "Payday at Coal Creek" Clayton
    22:50 "If I Had a Ribbon Bow" Glaser
    24:52 "When I lay down and I do die" Abrahams
    27:21 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR007, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0698; 28:12
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. Probably concluded on SR008.
    Start "Queen of Hearts" Roger Abrahams
    2:30 "Cannon Ball Blues" Abrahams
    4:30 "Paper of Pins" Paul Clayton and Gina Glaser
    7:15 "Cruel War is Raging" Clayton [Glaser and maybe Abrahams on the chorus]
    10:15 "Little Brown Dog" Abrahams
    12:15 "Handsome Molly" Abrahams
    14:15 "Locks and Bolts" Abrahams First line: I dreamed of my true love last night"
    16:55 "The Cruel Mother" Abrahams Also known as "Greenwood Sidey" or "The Lady of York"; first line: "There was a lady lived in York, all alone and lonely".
    20:40 "The Water is Wide" Glaser
    23:10 "Foggy Dew" Glaser She said this is a song from Ireland; first line: "A down the hill I went one morn"
    25:30 "Dink's Song" also known as "Fare Thee Well" Glaser First line: "If had wings like Noah's dove"
    28:12 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR008, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0699; 9:30
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. Probably the continuation of SR007.
    Start "I'll Fly Away" Roger Abrahams, Gina Glaser, Paul Clayton
    3:00 "Delia" Abrahams, Glaser
    5:35 "Been on the Job Too Long" Clayton [also known as "Duncan and Brady"]
    9:30 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR009, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0700; 15:23
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. All songs by Guy Carawan. SR009 through SR011 seem to have been recorded at the same performance.
    Start "The Water is Wide" Carawan
    4:00 Carawan talks about the summer he travelled in the South with Frank Hamilton and Jack Elliot performing and learning songs.
    5:35 [this is a version of the song "Simon Slick" or "Kickin' Mule"] Carawan first line: "My Uncle had an old mule, his name was Simon Slick"
    7:20 The first line is something like "Dedda Gelt Oy Yoi Yoi" Carawan This song is in Yiddish.
    10:20 [The title is probably "Wanderin"] Carawan first line: "My Daddy is an engineer, my brother drives a hack"
    12:33 "On My Way" Carawan
    14:08 "It's Me, Oh Lord It's Me" Carawan
    15:23 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR010, Recorded: 1958-04-08, RXG 0701; 15:45
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. All songs by Guy Carawan. Seems to be a continuation of SR009.
    Start Instruments on a Chinese bamboo flute Carawan
    1:04 "Chickens They Are Crowin'" Carawan
    2:20 Medley: "Hattie Belle She's My Own True Love" and "Look Down, Look Down That Lonesome Road" Carawan
    5:20 "Cripple Creek" Carawan
    8:10 Delia Carawan
    11:25 At the World Youth Festival Carawan learned a Russian song about a girl named Katushka[?]. Sung in Russian Carawan
    13:45 "Talkin' Atom" Carawan
    15:45 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR011, Recorded: 1958-04-08, RXG 0702; 15:45
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. All songs by Guy Carawan. The seems to be a continuation of SR009 and SR010.
    Start "Black Eyed Susie" Carawan
    2:10 "Railroad Bill" Carawan
    5:05 "Hava Nagila" [sung in Hebrew] Carawan
    7:30 Discussion of two Chinese instruments. One a pipe called a [Shang or Zhang] and a bamboo flute. Carawan
    10:10 This Land is Your Land" Carawan
    12:25 So Long It's Been Good to Know You" Carawan
    14:50 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR012, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0703; 30:51
    Good recording quality. This seems to have been recorded live, before an audience. All songs by Guy Carawan. This seems to be a continuation of SR009. Start through 14:45 is a repeat of SR011.
    2:05 "Railroad Bill" Carawan
    5:07 "Hava Nagila" [sung in Hebrew] Carawan
    7:29 Discussion of two Chinese instruments. One a pipe called a [Shang or Zhang] and a bamboo flute. Carawan
    9:25 This Land is Your Land" Carawan
    12:20 So Long It's Been Good to Know You" Carawan
    14:45 "Dance Boatman, Dance" Carawan
    16:25 "3 Little Pigs" Carawan
    17:54 "Sinner Man" Carawan
    20:02 "Old Blue" Carawan
    23:13 "He's Got the Whole World in His Hands" Carawan
    26:58 "Ontario" Carawan
    30:51 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR013, Recorded: 1958-05-25, RXG 0704; 32:01
    This is a recording for the second half hour of a John Dildine radio program. It features live performances by Tom Paley, John Cohen and Mike Seeger. It is the first time that these three musicians played together (see Allen, Ray – "The New Lost City Ramblers & The Folk Music Revival," University of Illinois Press, 2010, pages 38 to 40 and Malone, Bill C. – "Music from the True Vine – Mike Seeger's Live and Musical Journey," University of North Carolina Press, 2011, page 79). They went on to become The New Lost City Ramblers.
    Start Conversation by John Dildine: a recent concert by Pete Seeger; Announcement of upcoming concerts by Josh White, and by Tom Paley, and Bob Clayton. Introduction of Paley, Cohen and Seeger.
    3:07 "Soldiers Joy" Paley (vocal and guitar), Cohen (banjo) and Seeger (fiddle)
    5:15 "Weaver room Blues" Cohen and Paley
    8:30 Discussion of bluegrass and "greengrass" Seeger
    9:45 "Molly and Tenbrook" Seeger (vocal and banjo)
    12:18 Discussion of the song and banjo techniques Seeger
    14:03 "Make Me a Pallet on Your Floor" Cohen
    15:50 Discussion of John Cohen and his brother Mike Cohen who is a member of the Shanty Boys. Dildine and Cohen
    16:20 "Colored Aristocracy," instrumental Paley Paley says he got this song from a Library of Congress recording. [per page 39 of Ray Allen's book, this song is titled "Colored Aristocracy." The original tape box calls this song "Aristocrat ‘til I die"]
    18:00 Discussion of the song as a dance number. Comments about bluegrass.
    18:47 Tuning instruments
    19:48 "Boll Weevil" Paley (vocal)
    23:28 "Little Moses" Seeger (autoharp and vocal)
    27:50 Conversation: Dildine and Seeger about a TV program Seeger recently did.
    28:40 Dildine talks about this night's radio broadcast and upcoming concerts.
    30:08 "Railroad Bill" Paley (vocal and guitar)
    32:01 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR014, Recorded: 1958, RXG 0705; 12:50
    In this recording John Dildine interviews Tom Paley. The recording quality is very good.
    Start Paley describes how he got his first guitar in 1945 when he was in high school in NY.
    2:10 Paley talks about the kind of music he performs.
    4:05 Paley discusses where he went to high school, college and graduate school.
    4:40 Paley discusses how and where he learns songs.
    7:20 Paley discusses how he learned to play the guitar and the banjo.
    8:50 Paley discusses being influenced by "ethnic" or "authentic" performance styles.
    11:30 Paley discusses his recordings.
    12:50 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR015, Recorded: 1958-11-21, RXG 0706; 27:50
    Start "P Street Blues" Rick [Eric] Von Schmidt
    3:30 "Cindy" Hutch Morris and others on the chorus
    6:40 "Cambric Shirt" Jean Foss (vocal) and George Foss
    9:05 "DeKalb Blues" Von Schmidt
    13:45 "Henry Lee" Chris and Pixie Christie
    16:50 "Nottamin Town" Jean Foss (vocal) and George Foss
    19:45 "James A. Garfield" Von Schmidt
    26:09 reprise "James A. Garfield" Von Schmidt
    27:50 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR016, Recorded: 1958-12-02, RXG 0707; 29:01
    Good recording quality. This was recorded in the Dildine's living room. It is continued on SR017.
    Start John Dildine introduces and interviews Rudy Thurau and Ron Engh
    7:40 Introduction to "Annalisa" Engh
    8:30 "Annalisa" Engh and Thurau [sung in German]
    10:25 Discussion of rock and roll, and folk music Dildine, Engh and Thurau
    12:01 Introduction to a Dutch song Thurau
    12:55 [Dutch song, title not given] Thurau and Engh [sung in Dutch]
    14:22 Discussion of folk singing, conversation and cultural differences in Europe, the United States and Africa Engh, Thurau and Dildine
    24:15 Introduction to an [Algerian] song Engh
    24:50 [Algerian song, title not given] Engh and Thurau [language not identified]
    26:58 Discussion of the style in which the guitar was played; talk of busking in Africa Engh, Thurau and Dildine
    29:01 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR017, Recorded: 1958-12-02, RXG 0708; 27:55
    Good recording quality. This was recorded in the Dildine's living room. It is the continuation of SR016.
    Start Discussion of the way Ron Engh and Rudy Thurau look; they have beards. Engh and Thurau talk about singing in Paris.
    2:40 "The Shepardess and the Cat" Engh and Thurau [sung in French]
    3:45 Discussion of the pervious song. Dildine asks them to sing an American song.
    4:55 "The Fox" Engh (vocal and guitar), Thurau (harmonica) [sung in English]
    7:02 Discussion of their travels. Engh and Thurau built a raft and sailed down the Niger River. Engh broke his arm and had to return to the United States. The December 20, 1958 issue of the Saturday Evening Post will have an article about Engh and Thurau. They discuss the lecture/concert tour they are about to begin.
    15:57 "No, John, No" Engh and Thurau [sung in English; a variation of "No, Sir, No"]
    18:35 Discussion of previous song. Discussion of the languages they speak and don't speak. Discussion of their upcoming trip to South America, Australia, Japan and Asia. Dildine asks if they have made a record.
    25:00 "Bon Jour" Engh and Thurau
    27:55 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR018, Recorded: 1958-12, RXG 0709; 30:38
    Recording quality is ok; the volume level is uneven. It was recorded before a live audience.
    Start Introduction to the first song Sandy Paton
    1:45 "Coronation Coronach" [also known as "Scottish Breakaway"] Sandy Paton
    2:30 Introduction to the next song Sandy Paton
    4:10 "Cold Blows the Wind" [also known as "The Unquiet Grave"] Sandy Paton
    6:25 Introduction to the next song Sandy Paton
    8:00 A version of "Captain Wedderburn's Courtship" Sandy Paton
    9:40 Introduction to the next song Sandy Paton
    10:05 "Dear Companion" Sandy Paton
    13:40 Introduction to the next song Sandy Paton
    14:35 "An Old Man Rocking the Cradle" Sandy Paton
    17:38 "Dewy Dens of Yarrow Sandy Paton
    22:25 Introduction to the next song Sandy Paton
    22:50 "The Wild Mountain Thyme" Sandy Paton
    26:55 John Dildine thanks Sandy Paton, introduces Charlotte (Char) Daniels and announces a concert by Rudy Thurau and Ron Engh
    30:38 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR019, Recorded: 1958-12, RXG 017; 26:35
    2:04 "Lang a Growin'" Paton
    4:45 Introduction to the next song Paton
    5:35 "Long Time a Growin'" Paton
    9:35 "Keep That Wheel a Turnin'" Paton
    12:07 Introduction to the next song Paton
    12:40 "Charlie Mops" Paton
    15:30 "Sunday is My Day of Rest" Paton
    17:05 Introduction to the next song Paton
    18:25 "Foggy, Foggy Dew" Paton
    22:13 "Maids when you're Young" Paton
    24:03 Introduction to the next song Paton
    24:20 Several kid's songs: "Charlie Chaplin," "Shirley Temple," "Granny", "Duke Street Jail" and "Black-White-Cat" Paton
    26:55 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR020, Recorded: 1958-10-08, RXG 0711; 26:37